Emma Williamson emmawilliamson04@gmail.com

Residence: Bethune, South Carolina 803-427-2122 Cell

GPA: 3.7

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Athenaeum Press Conway, SC 2023 – 2023 Intern Loopy Lemon Cafe Camden, SC 2022 – 2023 Server and Hostess

KEY SKILL AREA

Creative Cloud (< 1 Year)
Troubleshooting (3 Years)
BBEdit (2 Years)
GitHub Pages (3 Years)
Project Management (3 Years)
JavaScript (3 Years)
Typing 75 WPM (3 Years)
HTML/ CSS (3 Years)
Social Media (3 Years)
Video Editing (6 Years)
Web Design (3 Years)
Canva (4 Years)

OBJECTIVE STATEMENT:

Soon to be graduate (December 2023) from a Bachelor of Arts program seeking a full time position where I can use my communication, research, and computer skills with the goal of learning and growing with your company.

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY:

My diverse skillset allows me to work effectively in many unique digital environments ranging from creating websites from raw coding and wix software, to developing and implementing social media strategies. With my experience in project management, I am able to work and manage multiple projects effectively at once and exceed expectations. Today, I possess thorough knowledge of the field of Digital Design with the ability to perform the creation of websites. I have a remarkable ability to communicate ideas and work independently and in groups.

EXPERIENCE:

Athenaeum Press

02/2023 - 07/2023

Multimedia Content Developer Intern

Experienced Multimedia Content Developer with a proven track record of developing multimedia content for events. Contributed as a member of a seven-person team to develop multimedia content for the 2022 Gullah Geechee Symposium. Assisted CCU Atheneum Press with the creation of digital content and a booklet for the annual event. Preserved digital documentation of African-American heritage in the region. Edited and transcribed videos for the digital content booklet, extracted pull quotes and side items for the digital content booklet, and designed flyers for upcoming events.

Loopy Lemon Cafe

05/2022 - 08/2022 and 01/2023 - 05/2023

Server and Hostess

Responsibilities included greeting guests and taking accurate food and drinks orders, using a POS ordering system. Performed shift duties such as rolling silverware, pre-bussing, and wiping tables. Ensured the timely delivery of food and beverages by checking on their tables throughout the shift.

EDUCATION:

BA Coastal Carolina University Digital Culture and Design Expected 12/2023